Get up. Live your day. Get killed. Again.
Happy Death Day is a comedy, horror, mystery film
directed by Christopher Landon.
Caught in a bizarre and terrifying time warp, college student Tree finds herself repeatedly reliving the day of her murder,
ultimately realizing that she must identify the killer and the reason for her death before her chances of survival run out.
Theresa 'Tree' Gelbman, played by Jessica Rothe.
Carter Davis, played by Israel Broussard.
Gregory Butler, played by Charles Aitken.
Lori Spengler, played by Ruby Modine.
Nick Sims, played by Blaine Kern III.
Danielle Bouseman, played by Rachel Matthews.
Happy Death Day is a 2017 American black comedy slasher film directed
by Christopher Landon and written by Scott Lobdell.
It stars Jessica Rothe and Israel Broussard.
The film follows college student Tree Gelbman, who is murdered on the night of her birthday but begins
reliving the day repeatedly, at which point she sets out to find the killer and stop her death.
Jason Blum serves as a producer through his Blumhouse Productions company.
Happy Death Day was released by Universal Pictures on October
13, 2017, and received generally mixed reviews.
It grossed $125.5 million worldwide on a $4.8 million budget.
A sequel, Happy Death Day 2U, was released on February 13, 2019.
The film explores themes of college, murder, time loop, slasher, young adult.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and mind_bending.